It's a beautiful day in the neighborhood a beautiful day for a neighbor
Would you be mine?
Hi guys
So further
Hi
That we're doing guys
Hey, Spongy. Here's the shopping center where I live.
Packed up.
Hey, this re-did it. This re-modeled it.
You can see a little bit of my neighborhood.
What's it up?
I usually run over here.
I know they're playing a Kelly Clarkson song real loud in there, so I had to mute it. This is where I get my nails done
There's like there's like there's at least two men in there
So people that say men don't get their their nails done
Pedicures or Manny's pedis
We didn't like construction. How's everyone doing?
Hey, Gaudi. Hey, Gaudi. What happened last night? Because I just heard, like,
you know, and I saw the clip of it and it's like, I'm not mad at you because, you know,
you didn't do it, first of all. And if you were laughing at it, it's like, it's like, I don't
You can react to, you can laugh, you're allowed to laugh at whatever you want, but what JT did was he was, he put up like animal beef reality, and then like also somebody's picture, I don't know what that was about.
I did fall asleep, right? On my stream, I was just gonna fall asleep, but you know what I'm talking about? We can talk about when I get back.
I didn't I didn't leave the stream
But I didn't like I saw the picture like I didn't I didn't know what it was like someone sent
Someone sent me the clip of my own show, you know, so I
Got it. So it was just weird. I saw you. I know I know I don't blame you
You know, you're just kind of laughing and you know, I don't
But he was going after this woman. I don't know if it was it was a Tiffany wears t-shirts or something like that
putting her photo up and then
and then say oh well
Report this bitch, and then he said you put like up a animal bestiality or something
Yeah, well, I don't blame you
Yeah, so I'm just gonna I'm gonna mute up all I go inside the store wait for a minute because
Like I said, like it wasn't you it wasn't you that did it, you know, I'll have to ask JT about it, but
Also, it was like
There are people from some other forum or something from a discord or something like all laughing about
You know how he was like, you know
They're like my show's gonna be
Striped because of what he's talking about and stuff and like I don't know and the people are saying
I know, I know you probably don't know what I mean to do with it, but
But there was in the base the bestiality, I don't know what it was like you describe it
Like it would I mean, I don't I don't even want to say that we're talking about other like kind of like, you know
Like I was the video wasn't age restricted
There's some kind of weird because like certain things were discussed in it. They were like some kind of weird
It was just give a definition of some term like it was just a kind of obscure
Like what was kind of like there was some kind of like some there's something this put something was just put on the video
Is that about something that was talked about it was not that too controversial, but it's like
There's people trying to get the correct definition. It's hard to describe
you know, but okay, so I
Mean I don't mind that he was talking I woke up and I heard it. I heard somebody saying I
being really objectionable or else like you know I would have like woken up more is like oh yeah
you know it sounded like he was just having a little little fun um you know he's just alone and
I was like uh what am I gonna do but and I miss the gaudy and the and the JT and stuff with them but
I mean, I think God, he behaved himself, I don't know.
Sometimes people, yeah, I don't like the idea
that he was discussing some of these controversial topics,
but you can actually discuss a lot of stuff on YouTube.
It's actually a lot more free than a lot of people think.
But it's not too, it's like, there are rules though,
and it's like, so that's why I try to,
Just stick to them as best as I can, you know
Keep my channel around for a long time. We got a lot of new subscribers. I want to be here for a long time
Just build up this channel
for success, you know the first like successful thing I've done in like a long time. Okay, so
Please try to support me on that
I would like people to like stand up and say hey don't you know don't show that
Okay
Yeah, hey you guys are bored with that music here
Okay, so hey guys
What happens
I don't know how, Gaudi's trying to be an I-pass.
It might be, I'm not sure.
I think I appreciate Gaudi in a wheelchair
with an I-pass and a Band-Aid on his head.
Ready to do a math, a man.
Not mass. I mean, I did I am vans a few people
You know
Someone some people send me some cash apps or got a cash up. So, you know, you know, I
Checked right away. I'm banned
Even if
Then my father I'll make me help and again. That's another cat. I mean, it's like if I have me
But I'm not gonna be up for no reason
I can't tell you how everybody do it.
Take a square where I can.
What's going on there?
This is something going on in my discourse.
Well, I said, what is that?
I don't know what that is.
It's like, it's kind of like,
That a woman
Okay, okay. Yeah, it's like
It's it's so it's like that you see the hoof
You don't see any nudity you don't see any penetration. It just looks like there's a woman giving a horse a piggyback ride I
Mean so
I'm not gonna show it. I mean it's like it's yeah, I
Don't know I mean it's
Yeah, I just see the
I see the hoof it's a it's a wraps in some they wrapped in some I don't know
Yeah, it looks like a woman is giving a horse a piggyback, right?
And then it's like all it all is to say a little close up of it. I don't I don't know I don't know what I'm looking at
Why why does he have that on his his anywhere? Why is he why is he?
It was the horse is right in the woman
Or maybe it might be a pony, I don't know it's like it's like it's like not like a not like it's like a
Huge, I don't I mean it's like I don't know I don't know
I just don't know what I'm looking at. It might be a goat. It was just like I just see like a hoof I
See a hoof and then like I see like it looks like kind of like it's like the kind of side of a woman
If you why do you have that why are you why are you watching that kind of videos? Okay
Midget in a horse costume, yeah
That's the animal to be I don't know guys
Mm-hmm
True God
No, it's anything like how you what I'm not there
Personals on the topics got kind of
you know dangerous and
And second of all, he did, but some women say as I told him not to change his profile photo several times.
Cassie says the dog
I'm sorry. Well, how did it go? I mean, I read some of the chat.
Oh, uh, oh, Nick is God who me. Oh my gosh, I must have been really drunk. Yeah, I got the one.
I'm God, I was just kidding. It's just fraternity, um, you know, locker room humor.
I
Was we go in there piglet
Usually come me a pig
I mean you're eating with your fucking mouth open. Come on, dude
Other ships the crunchy
Okay, how you doing there site did your boyfriend already leave what happened to Santa Claus?
No, you don't get to go. Yeah, where did your boyfriend go my boyfriend? Yeah, I
Think he's attractive. I don't you think he's attractive or you don't think he's attractive
I do he's a I just think he's a great personality and he's funny and he's also support of the show, so
Now he gives me
He gives me hey guys. I'm over here come to my channel vibes, you know
Well, it's okay people can support that he's never even as a promoter show
But if you I wouldn't people that check out everybody's channel. Yeah, you're right. He never asked you if he just does it
You know, I can't stand people like that bro and the other community I used to be in man like the fucking wrestling community
never you had like your own channel your own little community and you had to fucking pay for it
You had to pay for it to be fucking promote promoted
You can't be throwing out there channels communities without
What do you know?
You know, he has he has he had bought memberships for the show. He's supported the show. He's just uh, you know, so he's a
You know, there's your double standard because when
When you bring up supporting the show and I'm like, yeah, I've done it. You're like, yeah
Well, you know, you're all right. You've donated like five dollars once a year like, okay
But when he does it you're like, oh, no, he could promote he could do this you can do that you can do oh, yeah
You just
But you know and I know I've not only donated not only once it's actually a couple times
Do you give remote you're welcome to promote in the show
Well, I'm here to promote that nobody go to Dougie D's fucking channel. Fuck that guy
Arthur
Yeah, I don't know if I was a defender
Okay, anyway, how are you doing today?
Great, what chips are you eating?
See salt and I have a pizza bagel. I just picked up and I have a coffee. I'm gonna drink
Okay.
It's a vanilla cream.
Glow, glow, glow, glow, glow.
I've got issues apparently.
You're the one that has a fucking, uh,
a kid's dough as an avatar.
Okay, you're the one with the problems.
You're the one with the issues.
Apparently I've got issues.
You're the one that your name is fucking low-key, right?
That's your name.
And then also you're using the kids show as your avatar
I'm the one with the issue with the issues, but what kids show is that?
It's called Kim possible. Oh, oh, that's impossible. Oh, do you know the show?
Not really familiar. It's way past my
My time it wasn't even you know
Yeah, it's fucking weird like I find that weird using the kids show
As your avatars, I think you have issues about that. I think you have the issues
Well, you know what a lot of a lot of it
Adults like kids shows, you know, and some kids shows are like, you know
They're kind of like shows are kind of designed so the parents can watch them to you and enjoy them and you know
It's for some of them. I don't say like stuff like the powerpuff girls that has like a really interesting
Alchemical twist to it like you know, yeah, well, I'll throw it out there now. I think you have the issues
Lowkey, I think you're the weird one now what now what you're the one that's using the kids show as your avatar
I find that weird as a matter of fact, I find that very weird
You want to start throwing jackets and everything about that?
But you might think what do you think it's weird that I use like, you know, Disney
Villains cars awesome wonderland's cars. I mean is that weird they
That's like, you know cartoons. Well, I got no comment on that. You're no comment on that. Yeah, correct
Okay, let's just say
Yeah, we're in a weird guy. We can't even oh shit. We can't like we can't even enjoy like, you know
Disney cartoons as adults, you know, which we should know
I'm calm. I'm commenting, but you know, you said no comment like there's a no comment like oh the topic is
The topic is so taboo or so. No, it's TOS, right? Everything is TOS here. We got a tiptoe. Oh my god. No, don't talk about
You know, so well, uh, so are you a are you a monetized YouTube channel creator?
No, but I am in one. Oh, you're not. Oh, okay
You are one though. I'm respecting the TOS rules here, but yeah, do you know the TOS?
I have no I'm the one with the channel. I so I can like kind of say I'm probably
You've told me anything that's controversial
All I said is I like Disney movies that controversial. I mean, it's like you're like, oh no comment. It's a kid's topic
So that's why the kids are
Disney
I don't want it to be misconstrued. Well, anyways, I my point was that glow key is weird
For the one that's having a fucking kid's avatar. I think that's weird, but that was my only comment on that
Uh, you know what I found out and I'm gonna try to keep it as TOS appropriate as possible
um, yeah
Man like on twitter. I'm starting to see like a lot of stuff on the little hat people
Well, yeah, that's a little controversial. I know that's why I said the little hat that could be like yeah, okay
That could be so many people
Okay, all I'm gonna say is that they have some weird traditions and rituals
Wow, bro
Wow, and no wonder Google says no they don't do these things because if you put it in English
It's fine like yeah, okay. They don't do it
Because they do it in another way. So let's say you ask me
Psych, let's say you ask me. Hey, do you eat?
You ask me. Hey, do you like red apples? Do you eat red apples? And I'll tell you no, I hate red apples
They're disgusting. They're the worst thing in the world. How can you say that? I hate red apples and
Then you see me eating a green apple. You'll be like, well, oh my god
I thought you hate apples because you were like they're disgusting
And then I'll tell you corrections, like you asked if I like red apples, you never asked me if like green apples.
So...
they they misconstrue the words because it's in Hebrew wow man a lot of things
I'm starting to realize on the little hat people
let's not talk about it let's you know what I don't really care about for the
conversation I would love it there's like a channel out there in this
community that could just like has the money all the money that they don't have
to worry about oh my god I'm trying to make a penny a day you know feed me feed
I get it. I get it. No, I'm not. No, I'm not. No, I'm just saying I don't even I don't have anything to say about the topic
Yeah, so yeah
That's all I'll say though
It's like
Even this TOS is the topic I would not like to discuss
Okay
Okay, but I think you you are I think you're not
100% by I think you are a Jew, correct? No
Okay
You know the other day I was eating I went to a diner and I asked for some waffles and chicken and
My oh my
Have I been missing that the entire time? I've been born or alive
Chicken is amazing
Further good. Hey, he's trying to knock over my drink. Yeah
You know what I do love I love I love delis. I love
You know, I love I love a television
love the media I
love a
Love a potato pancakes
Nice
I hop around California
Yeah, we have an obstacle over here. Oh shit cool. What are your thoughts on white castle?
Why castle we don't really have any white castles around here, but do you have to the frozen
The white castle frozen burgers are decent
Do you have any eased the craves over there?
Hmm. We have mr. Beast burger
We have wall burgers mr. East mr. Beast
You have any Columbia and any Mexican any sushi any
Well, it's Los Angeles. Yes, so we have all those things we have all kinds of
Cuban and Japanese Chinese for days. We have a you know Greek restaurants. We have
Where I hate
like there's some restaurants like I guess you own certain areas and there's nothing against you I
just hated that it has to be like even brought up they'll have signs at the front of the door will
say gays are welcome or gays are always welcome or we love gays and it's like well why do you have to
I've never seen that. I've never seen that in my life
California you guys are the gayest state
Yeah, but I've never seen that and I'm maybe on pride month. They'll say though some some brats of business will flag a flag and like solidarity
on the area
But it's not for his fucking full lib tart over there
Well
I don't know. I've never seen anything that, you know, gays are welcome here.
I hate those types of signs, man. I hate them.
I think I saw a sign the other day. It was like, we are against ICE.
It's like...
Bruh, that shit cringes me the fuck out and mind you, I'm Hispanic myself, right?
So obviously I have family members that all day there I'll say because this community loves to
Love sister in the pot. I'm gonna say, you know, I have a couple family members that probably have some issues with ice
But Jesus Christ, dude, we hate ice
Okay
I don't really want to talk about politics. Oh my god this guy. I don't I don't want to talk about
I'm not talking politics, dude. Oh, yeah. Yeah, it is
Restaurants fucking being so like they'll bend over backwards for you just for your fucking dollar
Yeah, you know, you don't like that. I mean, you don't you don't see that you don't
Well, no, you're gay. You would obviously
Restaurants that are like welcoming. I know it's a you know a business can say they whatever they maybe they're trying to get a
Gate clientele or something like that or maybe that you know
I don't say it's just a 7-eleven a good old regular 7-eleven and they'll have signs with like we stand with BLM
It's like we know what you're doing. You just don't want fucking people to break in your story. That's all you want
Oh, I mean, who cares, some people agree, some people don't, who cares, they just sign them and say, people go whatever they want, and it bothers me, because it's just like, I prefer there being no sign, and it makes me think, you're just welcoming, the sign just has to say, welcome, that's it.
I don't know what I mean. I don't think I don't have to specify a certain group like oh, yeah, you know
This one little example of this one restaurant and you're like saying like oh, this is what it's happening
It's like I've never heard of any of that anywhere or before or I don't know never chat. Have you guys ever seen something like that?
Yeah, you're saying this is gay people are welcome or something like that. Do anyone see that?
I don't think so.
Bro, break.
Anybody in chat hall?
Wait, I want to see the response in the chat.
Well, someone has a laughing emoji.
We are outraged baiting you now.
Our bounty baiting veteran,
he gets second channel demonetized.
I see yellow people.
What does that mean?
Who said that?
Dogs, what does that mean?
No said that I'm trying to get you to add your channel taking down
Fuck you you fucking piece of shit. I've heard what you've had to say about same-an dude. Do not have scum a around dude
Why do you think his name? You know a lot of people?
What what's this saying? You have to listen to what they say about themselves, right?
It says it in his name. He's a scum a he's a scum asshole
You know, you got to watch out people tell you the truths
When they tell you about themselves when they tell you, you know, yeah, like I could be a piece of shit at times
Yeah, they're telling you right there. They're telling you they're a piece of shit
It's in his name scum a you got a raging demon. Well, it says it right there
You know, he's a fucking scumbag. He I'm gonna say I'm gonna I'm gonna you know
I'm gonna keep it keep it cool
to come a call to say man
You changed, right? You became somebody else for the better, right? Well, at least in that moment you did.
You know, you became somebody better, you were filled with positivity, and then as you progressed, I think you reached the point where you...
You you reach the maximum capacity of the limits you could do and you've gotten pretty good. You've gotten pretty well
And so now I feel like just because you're you're you've reached that maximum potential of you
Now you're like, you know what? I'm gonna go back to being a POS
Now I could go be a POS again because I know I'm not gonna be any better now. That's it. I'm and I can't get any worse
I'm already good
So now I'm gonna be a scumbag
Now I'm gonna call people the worst names in the book
You changed a lot scum
You've changed it a lot
You know
I've definitely given him a you know a chance because you know Zaya said some vile
Evil shit to him evil evil shit to him
Like Zaya was like, you know, I'm glad what happened to you. Now your wife sees you like this
And I hope she suffers or some shit, you know something in the in the in the world of those words
You know, he may have not said that exact quote, but he was definitely happy that
Scott may had this incident happen to him. And you know what?
I respect Zayn because at least he is as fucking brutal and as fucking scumbag
How much like no matter how much of a scumbag he is I gotta give it to him and at least
He's honest with it. You can hate him, but one thing you can't say he's a fucking liar because he's not
Now as of late, you know, obviously he's been
Fucking a brainwashed by
Babs, but my point was that you know
Zeta said some vile evil shit to scum a and I'm like yo like scum. I know who scum was
I found out who scum was what he did. Oh
And I was like damn man, I feel bad, but scum has been just I don't know man scum you you
You can't be changing up like this just cuz now you're better, bro. That's not good. You used to be different man
Got Murray change you got fun people
Yeah, because I don't know if you knew that he had an issue like he like some type of paralysis
But he got better from it
He got better and I think now I think he reached the limit to where that he got to his best
So now he's going back to his old
his old ways
Guys it's gone back bro
Yeah, anyway are there anything else interesting to say they go or at all. Yeah, definitely
Have you ever tried a Snapple banana?
Apple banana. No, is that a new flavor? Oh
My goodness. I love Snapple banana. Nothing like it. I
Want to snap I want to snap all your banana. I see there you go. There you go
there you go with that look
What does that even mean what does that even mean cause I'm always like I'm always talking about a topic and you're like
That's that's that's not inappropriate. That's that's inappropriate. Yeah, and then I'm talking about fucking
You're like I want to eat your banana
Yeah, so
Hey guys, the look we got KZ and number one was 75 XP
Scarlet number two is funky is number three
Guys you can still I don't know how you get more points or whatever says let me see it says
What's the leaderboard of a sleeve on this here? You got to act right now. All right?
This is
Here's how you collect XP you send message it in the chat and send super chat super stickers that I think
The top three get special badges in live chat recess every streams. You can always try again
I'll play as per fans to stand out in the community the top three but get special badges in live chat. Okay
That's pretty cool
You see like little crowns and stuff. So I guess a few oh here. We have a guest
I'm my name is Vargo ninja ninja
Look at my dog say hi mr. Murphy
Hi, there's Muffy look at Muffy
Joker you look more and more like a bum every day
Your dog talks to you
You know Amber Joker me and Amber go way back
She was my internet girlfriend for like one day
Yeah
He was just expected me two months
Joker that's real. I've seen I've seen embers hot house
Yeah
Kind of reminds me
Well, the new romance of the moment is flirty diamond and reaching demon. There's there's a new hot power couple on
The panel verse here. You want to see birdie? I got birdie here. Yeah
I've been wanting to find out more of like raging forgive diamond
Yeah, birdie's like three years old. She's the
She's a cutie man
She is a mix of black and white.
You see, she's a mix, she's black and white.
Amber is a mix of, I don't know what.
She has the N word pass, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
No, never say that.
I am, yes, I call it black.
Wait, wait, hold on a second.
Make a jump, make a jump.
Order that and make it like do-do-do-do-do-do-do.
Oh, my God.
I'm a DJ, what can, what can, what can?
You guys want to see my glasses?
Yeah.
Please.
Oh, God.
You look like...
Aren't I awesome?
I want to put those glasses on my, you know...
Dog.
On your dog.
On your butthole.
Okay.
See you.
Bye.
Joker is a cute one time. He did it one time. He did he's still on his head for me and I thought
He Joker dropped off. I'm sorry Joker. I was just kidding
I
Don't know maybe just maybe just accidentally disconnected or
You just want to stop by a few
Emory you have to tell you have to tell psyche to go
Hey, I tell psyche
What are we what are we doing here? I don't know what I have to tell psyche
What are we doing here? I don't know space launch
I'm confused. I'm so fucking confused right now. Me too. Oh my god. She doesn't get it
Dark Shrekers
Everyone already knows the game
About me getting a trouble
No, we're not bad. It's because psyche has a fucking it looks like he's ready to fucking launch off
Oh, yeah, my headset my headset. Yeah, it's my thing. It's my thing. I do the psyche
From Texas
What is that? Oh
I was attacking you
Yeah
Taking it off my hands
Oh, you're welcome.
Mr. Gowdy's man.
It looks like he's like launching off into space or something.
I love it.
They're like, people say mine look like a call center.
Yeah, like you're a telemarketer or something.
Yes, exactly.
It's like, you hear you scamming that?
No.
I mean, you do sometimes it's a little
Morbid you've already told
You see how many likes do I have I have ten like no hey you
the
You're a little emotional, but you're not scared. There's nothing wrong with being emotional. I think I think people should be more
Emotional so they don't come off as fucking serial killer
Yeah, I know
Serial killer type
Who you
What are you doing?
Because you're emotional too
What do you mean?
There's nothing wrong with being emotional people just associate
When you say emotional people
But you think what do you think yeah, I express yeah, I mean I'm an expressional type of person you are too
Yeah, but
And like wrap people up in fucking burlap sacks
I don't think you do that. Do you do that? I I've never said that but can't you do that?
That's what I'm asking you. I mean
Yeah, but that's serial killer status. Oh
You're saying by psyche
Hi, bye. Love you later
Later love. Thank you. You know what? Aren't you supposed to say that to girls now like later love?
Bye love you Amber
Are you just up here to
Did you say ice monkey
No, bye Sponky
It's going on everybody
We're boring
I
Because she was
What is Arthur's what everyone says they're not leaving what is Arthur's what is Arthur saying the discords go
Amber was tricking it
There I can't hear you. This guy has no radio etiquette. What did you say?
So Arthur are you are you are you on Sam as discord talking about me, but right now? No
Okay, what are you? What are you saying this guy doesn't have a radio etiquette?
I don't think I'm talking about Sam as this board. He keeps talking over bro
Okay
He's a douche, yeah, I know what's going on say no manners
He's trying to get close with fucking psyche, that's what he's doing
It's like I have to ask you a question like people have to talk to you. I know that these people were lawyers
I'm lower than you
I'm a lawyer
You got the lawyers. Oh my gosh, did she just say she won because that's illegal to say something
To say you're a lawyer
I said I'm a lawyer what's been what's been hot man? How you been dude? I'm gonna go with that right now
Okay, why okay?
What do you mean why and you claim to be a lawyer?
legally I
Can represent myself in court therefore I'm a lawyer it said no it is not generally
That's stupid
It is not that Bundy tried that and look how he turned off. I think what you're trying to ask is it a crime?
To represent yourself you're done dude. I'm telling where's your home? I'm telling the Oklahoma police department. You're done
You got two narks we got two narks on channel, okay
I'm sorry, that was funny.
Yeah, but it wasn't a crime, I can represent myself so I'm a fucking lawyer
Well, she keeps claiming to be one psyche. I don't think that's to us appropriate. It just said it's a crime
It is a crime scum. Why are you attacking me?
Scum get up here hurry up
And by the way, Ikea like the good
I can't stand these two on 10 I can't stand you you're lying right now you're
knocking on the nark right now I don't like it what I don't like it what did he
just say you're not he's calling you a little bitch because you're gonna tell
the Arizona Police Department like that's a thing that I'm representing
myself as an attorney illegally David you and hang up on you
And besides, there is no Arizona Police Department,
there's city departments, then there's state departments,
but even then, you still have to find the state like office
or location near me.
So I dare you to fucking call the Arizona Police Department
and I'm done.
I do it.
Oh, right now clipped in shit, cold.
Call him hurry up
Arthur what does it feel like to get destroyed constantly by a method where is psyche yet?
So I just trying to go to sleep
Arthur yeah, I mean man you're narkin on a nark so that makes sense, right?
I'm waiting to go to work. I just wanted to join a channel.
Yeah
Today
You're the whole steak
I'm not doing anything. I'm not even talking about you. I'm not doing I literally have been staying out of the fuck shit
I don't even know why you blocked me like I haven't done anything
Would you eat today? Don't pay attention to chat. I'm asking you. What did you eat today?
And it is like a steak
Number eight anything
I haven't eaten anything here, because as soon as I woke up I had to do some schoolwork and I decided to make kiddos.
Every woman says that and then actually when it comes down to it they're like, yeah, I ate like big bars.
I really haven't eaten anything today. I'm gonna sit here a little bit more.
Ziggy, aren't you the dude that was claiming false shit on Say Man 2? Don't you do that?
I don't know anything about Say Man, nope.
Hmm
Be a real tragedy if I find out something about you and we get oh wouldn't be a real tragedy if you fucking dialed me in and fucking
I found out something about you
Wouldn't that be threatening?
Are you threatening to like gobsm or go relay what you're doing? Yeah, I didn't say doxin
I said I'm gonna find something out just to get a man from here
Because I think he did
Yeah
I'm gonna get banned from the site just because
LD15 can put a dog and not even get banned from here. So what the fuck good luck with that
Did you just know it sounds like he's gonna be like
I don't know anybody can make up anything like that whenever I was whenever I was trolling
I would say like this troll is
Or this this mod is fucking timing me out too much and fucking like then I would get that fucking mod
So anybody can oh
Now you know don't trust the video in the chat
Right, of course not
I'm not trolling but
There you go. He's in troll anymore just now now. He just doesn't troll anymore now now. We got to believe him
I'm a good boy. Oh my god. We got all listen to him now make sure he's not he's not lying
He's reformed I think we were fucking
You want me to go back to my old ways?
Yeah, if anybody knows Amber knows I'm fucking reformed. What are you doing?
You must be new to this
Dick to me and then he saw my cleavage and then he was nice and now he's a dick to me again
He didn't see my cleavage in a while. So we forgot why he liked me
Oh, send it send it to him again. It's kind of like a re-upload. You know?
Ziggy, Ziggy. Shut the fuck up.
No. Send it to him anymore.
I'd send him back his memory with my cleavage and maybe he'll be nice to me again.
If you send him more, he'll fucking relax and fucking...
Ziggy, you can't stand me, dude. I can't stand you.
I can't stand you. And I don't even know you. But I do like you. You're okay.
I
Don't like salmon doesn't mean I don't like you that's my twin. You're talking shit about my twin. I come for you
Do you like Arthur I think he's
Um, uh, I thought you were just talking about Samman and Arthur.
No, Samman broke him. No, fuck no.
But do you like Arthur?
Oh, no, no, but this is Aldo.
This is Aldo.
This is Arthur!
I know this is not Aldo. I'm not gonna play along with that retardin' shit.
Never did you have to go did you have to like crannies or something?
You crayons you tarred
You did on camera one time you did
I've never eaten a crayon like pot. No, it was like a cake shit. It looked like it was crayons
Oh, I've definitely eaten food on screen, but I've never eaten food.
Samman, I got you, I'll ask him right now.
Ziggy, what's this whole deal, UNJT?
What's all that about?
What do you mean?
I don't know.
What?
What's going on?
Tell me.
What's happening?
Like I said, we got people out here.
They know stuff, bro.
What?
What's up?
Yeah, tell me what's up.
Again, you threw false accusations towards Sam and and I'm gonna get your band. That's my job
You're not gonna get a band from psyche psyche. Let's anybody rock
But once I get the proof and the screenshots you're done, dude
It was it was crystal Marie was saying that to say man. I didn't do that
My
What do you mean JT
Psychi, what are you doing?
Thank you, you got a couple of blacks up here
What
Like black and like iron plates
like our employees this is what I did today what is that the fuck it's a
Dutch bro's
God
One chick
You didn't turn into that one chick that fucking gives to that one place with coffee every day. They do. What's her name?
I can't remember. I got a best friend every day before work. Yes. I've got a bag from them. I've got a bunch of pickers
I've got a cup holder
I have no idea who you're talking about
Yeah, dude.
Don't do that.
What the fuck was that noise?
Crissa.
What was that?
Excuse me.
Something.
It is sassy, and it's so good.
It's called Shark Attack.
Oh my god.
There's so many Starbucks people in here.
What did that guy leave, man?
He left.
He didn't get far.
Are they left?
I know I got to get off in a few minutes, too,
because I got to go to work.
I did, too.
Yeah.
Well, what was that?
I almost closed that on the screen.
That's what it was.
Anyways, I just wanted to join panel and I never really get time to join panel and I had a little bit of time before I go to work
And he's like he was dying so I'm like I'm gonna fuck a joint
Thank you very well, or you're a ziggie or no
Do I what? Have you had Ziggie before or no?
Well, yeah, me and Ziggie go way back. I've seen his penis
Oh, you have okay
Listen he has a nice he has a nice penis even when he was a fucking piece of shit to me
I still said he had a nice penis
You know who else has a nice penis and it's like a waste of a penis good times
It's a shame that it's attached to him.
Have you seen it?
Like you sent a photo of it or how?
I've seen it before.
You're showing it, OK.
Well, you do that.
You know what I thought about that, so.
They have a motor dick, right?
And he's like, motor dick.
And I can't think of anything.
I know.
Actually, so you remember Chris?
Yeah, you remember Cringesorius,
Like this have like a wall of streamer dicks where she gets molds of their penis. I think that's an amazing idea
Yeah, I remember
I'll do it. You still stream I
Know you will and you have a nice penis so but that's what I'm saying like good times like a shame
So don't let diamond like don't be like
Thinking that that was diamonds thing diamond like I had to have heard me talking about it one time
I heard crystal talk about her beat talk, but that's my thing. I rate penises and I do for free. I don't charge $25
She's under she's undercutting diamonds diamonds penis rating business. Oh, but does it tell me more about JT's though?
So tell me what like you send me a photo. What was he doing in the photo has he nicely groomed?
You know, it's very hard because most people they send pictures of their penis
You just see the penis and like the top of the shorts. Well, like good times
It was really funny because he was on like his lawnmower
Like you could tell he was outside on his righty.
What if he is bent over all this shit?
I don't know. I couldn't really tell that much.
It was like peeking out of the top for the overalls or was it overalls down a little bit?
Wow, we're talking about good parts.
I don't know if I can see the balls.
Okay, you can see the balls.
Okay.
But I want to know about Ziggy.
What about Ziggy?
Tell me, like, how was Ziggy's photo?
Ziggy's was nice.
It was kind of dark, obviously.
It was it was like a dark
What the fuck are you talking about?
The picture itself was dark. It wasn't like hella bright lit up
Okay, yeah
It's like a nice girls and a nice like like links
Was he fully hard?
I mean
Wait hold on if you're gonna take a dick pic I wouldn't imagine that you would be hard wouldn't you?
Yeah, ZZ. Are you gonna send one to me? Are you gonna send that photo to me?
Are you gonna send that photo to me on discord?
That way, buddy. No, no
Who the fuck wants to see that
Yeah
Ziggy's penis definitely took to at least it took more than two hands to cover it
Wow, okay
Okay, all right
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Something something breathing hard to the back
Yeah, it's like you have an old oil engine for an air conditioner or something
It blows hard, okay.
I mean, just like you can like sit and sweat. Is that what you're saying?
Ziggy, you said you're a dickfake, too. 67-year-old woman, too.
Ziggy, you said you're a dickfake, too. 67-year-old woman.
I love you, Mrs.
I'll see you inside. Sorry.
Bye, Amber.
Thanks for stopping by.
I'm not leaving yet. I've got like 10 more minutes.
Okay. Okay.
Well, Platform Boost says Ziggy sent his...
He says his dick pink to a 67-year-old woman. That's who's Ziggie
But what I mean
What's wrong with that?
You think there's other people Ziggie?
I'm definitely send my dick to yeah for sure. Well, how many people have you shared it with? Oh
women
numerous
I
He's not gonna answer
And and like rusty's the one that's like
Me a back in that picture
You said you said you said one to rusty
I did yeah stupid
People like to give me shit cuz I flash you dig and fade it cuz they're 19, but they're fucking over 18
So I show my tits to whoever the fuck I want to as long as they're of age
85 year old I don't give a fuck
Yeah, I've always ever like if I've ever sent you a dick pic dude your way
Honestly, I'm 39 man. I always send it to the fucking people that are all of me
Well, I just went on the panel and flashed if I didn't I didn't send like a picture of my taste
I just went on panel, I'm sorry, I'm sorry that Rusty, I'm sorry that Rusty doesn't like Dick, my bad.
That's why she keeps bringing up. What a bitch. That dumb thing.
And that's one thing I can say of all the dick pics that I've been sent.
I don't. I haven't shared them
around except for there was I
there was one and that was
Prini is and that's because he
denied sending me his dick pic.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
But, uh, he didn't like sending us dick pics, so I was like, uh, I don't fucking think so.
I mean, like, that's not, I don't know, maybe I'm a hippie at fucking life or something.
Hey, if you're older now, and older than me, because I like older women, I like bigger women.
Yeah, yeah.
So.
I know you're just some big bitch.
Mm-hmm. Oh, hell yeah. Yeah
Every day I don't even understand I don't even get it like I don't even get how I get hit on every day
But I think it's my personality too
Your personality because you also dude
Stop doing the fucking personality thing not just that but you were singing you remember that
Yeah, I see
Right. I love it. And they heard me sing here too. So I'm going to sing
She's a good singer. She really is psyche. She's a fucking good singer
Oh, thank you
Mushrooms in there I went
Can you read my favorite song?
My favorite song to sing?
He won't mod anybody, dude.
He doesn't even...
Dude, it's like he doesn't even...
Dude, I've asked.
He doesn't even fucking...
I told Kate to mod.
I know it's like he won't mod already.
Are you asking what my favorite song to sing is
or my favorite song to listen to?
You're absolute...
No, no, no.
Now, here we go.
You're absolute.
Favorite song ever? Country, rock, metal, anything? What is it?
It's such a tough question.
I know.
I think my all-time favorite song is The Fool by Leanne Walmart.
Oh fuck that's country. Holy shit. Yeah, that's like my absolute favorite song
Wow, okay
What's that or do you just knew you just knew it was country because of Leanne Womack or do you know this song?
No, I know the song. Yeah. No, I grew up on that shit
Literally, yeah exactly
My favorite one I could do in karaoke is
Cold no one that is and it means so much
God
No one's breathing
You need to go and die boy
Girl, whatever the fuck you are
Right I'm fucking hate that thing
I
Said a dick one time and oh my god like everybody fucking dies five years ago get the fuck out of here platform boots
Stupid fuck you dumb fuck
Eat that bitch man. She's so stupid that woman is so dumb
And even worse even
Dude check it out Ember even worse
She has my fucking little dumb ex now
Following her
That's stupid of me. Ah, guess what you're now my ex
Yeah
Jan is my ex. She's gone. She follows that fucking rusty idiot. No, thank you. I'm good
Jan's chicken army
Good good, but she follows the wrong people
Yeah, yeah, but this thing
All right, I love you guys I am gonna get off here. You're going to work now. So thank you. Thank you
She said bye you gotta say like that too bye
Later man
Hey, Rusty. Oh, yeah, don't fucking let Rusty fucking do we're on the man side Rusty
Yeah, you were over on the girl side. Don't fuck around man
Rusty's crazy. Yeah, she's a nutcase. Have you noticed that? Yeah
No comment
What a weird
What are you doing you fucking rolling a fucking tobacco
How opinion pizza oh
Pizza was on jalapeno bagel not bad
Yeah, but it's basically
Yeah, just pizza
Oh, yeah, dude, um, let me get with you right here right right now
The the the pizza fucking pieces
like two T knows pizza
bullshit, is it combination cheese or
Don't know. I really don't get those. I like you know either make my own right get these never bought those
I don't have my
Really don't have my freezer
But if you go choose would it be cheese supreme or fucking
Combination or pepperoni. I don't want to ask rusty
No, no, let me see. Let me get a bigger. Oh, look how big we are. Oh
Yeah, to Tino's the pizza, what would you do knows we can
No, I like
I like to meet when there's some meat inside of it. Oh
Three meat
Yeah, I'm too me that should be a millionaire youtuber drama to assume you're first. I'm gonna call it
Are you bringing a millionaire YouTube drama to the stream yard verse?
Yeah, Rusty is I'm sure yeah, she always brings drama to everything. Yeah, she's crazy
Witch little witch
There's a millionaire
You know, no, she's not a millionaire fuck rusty. No
No, I don't know, but what's the millionaire you should use you for drama me?
Feel like we can just do all the better fucking creating. Yeah
No, you know, it's like
You just eat raging demon and I'm sorry diamond on the stream
That was funny. Yeah
Maybe we're going to try it
Have you ever been with the trans?
No, no, fuck no, I haven't no
You would never know fuck
No, I wouldn't
Are you are you give a girl? No?
Okay, so no rusty rusty scared my girlfriend away. No, no
Does rest rusty want you for herself or?
No, she's like a man hater. That's all it is. She's a man hater
Well, okay, so so you met a beautiful beautiful like a bombshell
Like she's she's exactly what you want and she then she says well when I was 18. I
Hypothetical yeah, yeah, and she said when she was 18 she underwent gender reassignment surgery and
You know and you know you can't really tell the difference so many and you found love so but then you find out about that
So what'd you do?
Freak out and throw him in a creek
I mean if they didn't tell me
Forehand I would be
You're telling you beforehand you just
No, thank you. No, no, I like women. I'm a guy that likes women
Like scum like scums down there. He's actually dude. He's not a man. He's a woman
Don't as a woman. Yeah, what do you mean? You didn't know that scum was a woman
Really? How's though?
No, he has woman parts, but he went and did his thing to you know that shit to turn himself into a man
Scum scum you are
Yeah, yeah, are you sure?
2000% yeah
Scum is the most come
But I see he's real hair. He said he's he's Rosie O'Donnell
Yeah, he's real Harry. He's real Harry and I think I almost thought his balls. Yeah, I'm almost all balls
Yeah, no he has balls
All I'm dreads. I mean no I said balls. Oh
Yeah
They do
Stories about the Belzer legendary
Yeah, she just told me I'm Amber just told me they're they're big
No, she told you that my dick was big
Oh
Okay, are they so they're not big
What?
Yeah, your balls are not like everything big like yeah
Okay, okay
I'm talking about scum though like he's he doesn't have any balls. He doesn't are you sure how you see him?
No, it's a big giant like it's kind of do you know what's it?
Whenever they have surgery into it, you know, that's it's gonna have surgery. It's gonna have surgery
They whenever they have surgery man, like it's a phallus thing. It's weird. I know but no, but but you're saying you're saying scum
Come has a big pussy. Okay scum. So it's like are you
So it was a gate a gate. Yes
Oh, it's just coming to a born a female or a male
Female wants to be a male
Okay, that's look right there. He has a big pussy, right?
Come was a woman two years ago
Right gosh
Okay, I didn't know it's guys, you know, so you're like many Manson scum. So I think you should I want you to dread your hair
Yeah, fuck. Yeah, yeah
Long as I believe I believe that as long as you have hair. I think you should fucking dry it. Yeah, absolutely
I know I don't judge no matter what, you know, I accept you for who you are. No, hold on
He said he's a born male now. He said these boys guys. No, I'm just
Said he's born male. Are you just it's all messing with me
No, he's actually born a female. I'm talking. I don't I don't I don't
He's seen my dick dude like in it. Well, she I should say she
And she's gum wanted
Man, what is it? What is the profile? What is that in the profile photo? What is that?
What is it? I don't know what you're doing. It's rusty on there. Is it rusty?
probably she's crazy yeah she's in that bag guys chat okay well I don't think it's
anything hey Rusty are you here you cannot hear you
Yeah, it's funny isn't it. Here she comes. Watch her attack me. Let's get ready. So Ziggy said you a dick pic. Yeah.
How was it?
Not not not not thrilling that's for sure. Oh
Well, the other woman said that it was
If I was into if I would have been into it and requested it it would have been different, but I didn't
And five years ago, that's the problem. I don't care how long ago it was. It was five years ago
Have you not watched porn between them?
What does that have to do with it?
What does that have to do with anything?
You haven't seen the dick.
No, but Ruchy, did you ask him for the photo?
Did you ask him for it, or did he defend it to you?
No, I didn't.
So let's get it out of the blue.
Yep, that's right.
Were you just like, were you flirting at all?
I was flirting with her.
She wasn't accepting my flirting.
Never.
Nope.
Right.
No, but I'm going to give him my email.
So that's how I got it.
He sent it to me.
That's like the first thing he sends is a dick pic.
I mean, it's like.
I told him I'm old enough to be his mother. That's one of the issues. I'm like, you know, almost 30 years old.
I'm not old enough to be my mother. What are you talking about?
Yeah, yeah, that's what he doesn't believe because I look young and I act young.
Well, then how old are you then?
My chronological age is, you know, not really...
The way that I am on on panels or whatever so yeah, but how old none of your fucking business
I just told you I'm old enough to be your mother. Yeah, I'm almost 30 years older than you
Wow
When he begged to talk to me
The time goes on, you know, so I said no, I'm absolutely not interested in you
Crushed on me and then I started going to Jarls stream the guy
And talking about me all the time as if I was available to him. That's what he does. He starts shit with everybody
That's what he does. Yeah, well, yeah, I'm not sure like
She is
But the rest, do you have a collection?
I mean, do a lot of guys send you photos?
No.
I don't do that stuff.
And most of the time, I've been involved with somebody
online that people knew about.
And then when I wasn't, I'm not talking in private to any dudes.
I mean, we talk private.
And I gave him my yeah, it just like all these other people when you get mad at somebody that you're seeing online or whatever
And then maybe you know, you might talk to someone else to make them jealous or whatever
Rusty is the type of person Rusty's literally a man later email because he kept going up
He kept going up on my ex-boyfriend stream constantly talking about me and nobody would defend me
Even the guy that he was going up on their street on his stream
He never said, hey, don't talk about my woman like that or anything like that, like nobody ever defends me. So I just, you know
I let him have my email and then he sent me an unsolicited dick pic, which he was
Everyone there's
Women that he that he sent his unsolicited dick pic to you at the time
So I was just like another another woman in line for it, you know, yeah, unsolicited that means you didn't ask for it
You're not a person
Unsolicited means uninvited unsolicited means uninvited unwanted
No, that's why I'm suffering the consequences because you are fucking leading fucking Jen now. Yeah
About me. Yeah. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, this is what you
I will get you so I just
I just talk about you, however, I want to talk about you.
I refrained when she talked about me all day, baby.
She made an effort in her life.
I still think that you are pretty.
I really like your face.
I like your face.
Well, she made a mistake.
She's going to be talking about me at all to you.
That's what her mistake is.
And that's what you have her broken up.
Accept you as however you are, all of your alcoholism, and all of your fucking bulls that you do with other women,
and he accepted you, and she gave you a chance to live her life, and you are a fucking loser here.
If you're a fucking loser, it's gonna get rid of you.
No one else, so when you are together...
I refrained from talking about you anyway.
Why are you still talking?
I refrained from talking about you.
You always talk.
You were just talking about me.
No, no.
When you were together with her six months ago or whatever,
I refrained from talking about you at all.
I'm real pissed at you, buddy.
I'm real pissed. You've worked the contract. I said that I wouldn't talk about you
Whenever you asked me not to talk about you out of your relationship. I wouldn't you wrong
You brought me up
And now I can talk about you any time I want
Shit, I don't fucking like you.
I told you not to talk to me.
I know you don't.
Clearly.
You're like, we're Batman, here we are.
I told you.
You're talking about me yesterday.
You talked about me and Zen stream all day yesterday
and you got your ass.
You're damn right.
I'm going to talk about you every day, honey.
Well, I talk about you every fucking day.
And I don't care how Jen feels about it.
Every fucking day.
No wonder Jarl fucking hates your ass.
Why? Why? Why does he hate my ass?
You're a fucking weirdo, dude.
Why? Why are you weirdo?
You attach yourself to things.
Oh, I attached myself to a guy that talked to me every single day of his life.
And now you hate every man in life.
You hate every man in life.
I don't hate my boyfriend absolutely. Well, I only need to like one man and that's the man
I'm involved with and that's not you like a lot of women
Yeah, I do I like and and and you're dumb women follow you
Because I open the door to talk to Jan because I I she asked
I refuse to talk to her out of deference to both of you. I didn't want to be in
You have to do anything. I already know how you are. I don't give a fuck about you
You're a complete fucking scumbag
Scumbag, you're the one that fucking gets fucking
You're by yourself!
I don't know how it is, because I've been on
You are by yourself!
It's always how it is
You're always by yourself
If the girl was here right now, he would say
Yup, I fucking really love her because she sucks
Everything about me
So, that's the greatest thing that's online.
Don't hold us.
Yes, and you got told too.
I don't have to say anything because everyone's going to know right now what the fuck is about you.
What?
We're talking.
I'm not hiding anything.
Who wants to be with a loud mouth like this? Raise your hand. No one who wants to be with
a fucking controlling piece of shit fucking drunk chicken farmer who lives in his grandpa's
fucking barns. I don't live in my grand. I don't know what the grandpa thing is. What
the hell is that? This shit, this fucking piece of shit doesn't even have fucking plumbing.
This is out the fucking door, out the barn.
Look at her.
My own house.
Jam doesn't know.
Dude, I have my own fucking house.
No, you don't.
That's why I don't fucking let you know where I live.
Now my grandmother
You live in your grandparents fucking basically their outhouse
They built a fucking lean to you for you to fucking live in with your chickens
You don't have to you're enabled to be a fucking piece of shit
Piece of shit
Chicken oh, yeah
Yeah, you are oh, but there was this woman named Jan Marie who actually saw
Opened your fucking life to you and opened your door
That can hold a job it has her own fucking she has her house she has her own house you don't
You're a dependent, not my own house, piece of shit, you're a fucking loser, you're a woman abuser, but that's because you're a fucking, you're a man hater, you're a cocaine addicted alcoholic piece of shit, I am not on cocaine at all, but if I was, you're a fucking loser, you're just a loser.
Okay, well then tell her that and see if you guys can be best friends.
You're old enough to be working for a living, you should be working for a living, and you
will be the best friend of course.
You blame whoever it was, Lockheed or whoever it was, laid you off and then you never got another job because you've never worked for Lockheed.
Well whatever the fuck it was, I don't know.
What the fuck are you talking about?
Some security company or whatever. You're un-pirable.
You are an un-hier-al, un-employ-able, fucking piece of shit bum that-
And you said Lockheed, and then you're gonna tell me that I have no house.
Your friend here is in a fucking lean-to that they used to fucking dig a hole in the ground and put a piece of wood over it to take a shit in.
That's where you live
It's funny. I would like that, but that's not true. Why are you wasting your breath all the time?
I would love to fucking have you over and fucking have you in my clubhouse rusty
You're an idiot
You're an idiot, I'm not available, I've never been available, I've never been available to you, any other man, any other man, I'm not available to any man, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero
You want to be her number one, so you're a fucking hero.
You're a fucking one, that's all right.
You're a fucking nothing. You're a nothing.
All right, that's great.
Why don't you fucking keep talking to her?
She named her chickens after you, by the way.
Yeah, I noticed that. That was really nice.
Really cute. Really cute.
Sounds like I don't blame me for your fucking relationship failure. You made it fail you and only you
that woman gave you her time her efforts and her emotions and you shit all
You keep I have interruptions
I never said
Interruption
She heard me talking about you.
She heard me in the beginning.
And as soon as you started getting involved,
I fucking said, I'm not gonna say another word
about these people.
I'm not gonna talk to either one of them.
I want them away from me, right?
So I did nothing.
I did nothing.
I did absolutely nothing.
Oh, like you did with, what's her name?
I did nothing! I did nothing! I did nothing!
No, you never did anything.
You are such a fucking piece of shit.
You never did anything, Rusty, ever.
You never did anything.
You're a fucking loser.
You're fucking grandfather's outhouse.
I mean, why are you even calling my grandpa out, dude?
That's weird.
Why would you even like talk about my grandfather like that's weird
By rusty
I
Thank you, where you at?
So good
There's my boy
Gonna put his helmet on
What a fucking cunt
Hello
Hey
What's up? What's up, man? Yeah, I think I'm in that
long story short we have a little woman and
It's the most every day and fucking here we are
Rusty are you hope you're doing okay? What's up? Noble Castro? Hey, be da. Hey Oliver
Hey, everybody. Hey, you can the you'll in the wheel Hannah
Scott oh, yeah, fuck. Yeah, I'm gonna put a stone at this bitch. Oh, yeah, fuck. Yeah
What are you saying? What are you saying?
Do what remember that song I'll put a spell on you remember that yeah
I'm gonna put that that's what I was saying in chat like I'm gonna put a
Thank you. Thank you, Castro
Wait, what kind of spell are you putting on her? Are you gonna mix your steaming in some like a spaghetti sauce or something?
No, what the hell are you talking about?
Oh, okay. Well, let's see what we're about.
She's crazy. She's a nutty one.
Let's see, are you there?
Let's see. He's talking to things magic on you.
Man, no, did you know mr. Mr. Big pipes is um, dude
You do
Yeah, well he was using his
He was using his profile picture and someone alerted me to it. They're like, oh, he's using a chaos chaos magic sigil as this profile picture
I think you know I didn't know exactly what it meant, but he just kept kind of put they try to shove it in my face and so I
Blocked him and then he wrote in my back chat. He's like, I'm hexing you six six six and he's like you're done
I'm a powerful. I'm a powerful wizard at all. I mean, oh, it's like weird stuff
And so I know that was a lot and then he could already come back
But then he just comes back with that sizzle and then he doesn't say anything. He just like sits silently
So I don't know
That's this weird bitch man. She's like that with me because she hates man. She really hates men
That's what she is.
Well, you hate women.
I mean
That's what you display. That's what you display. That's it. That's a very much a hallmark of men when they think
When there are abusers and they think that showing a woman
Like
Unsolicited dick pics is actually
in that five years and I'm like and I've never said a fucking thing and that's what you do
that's what a lot of men do they think it's a fucking gift to give somebody an unsolicited dick
That's how guys are I didn't grow it. This is the problem with me or whatever
I'm older
Everything
And I'm not talking about this at all, as much as this fucking dildo, look at this.
I didn't even get an unsolicited dick pic or any kind of dick pic until the last five
years of my life.
All right, wait.
Hold on.
Did you do those kind of things?
Like, does this fucking shit happen?
I want to ask you one more time.
But millennials, like this asshole, it's just, it's just calm in place.
It's just calm in place.
Take your time electronically or tits or whatever, but I don't come from that. I don't come from that
Hey be quiet. I'm talking to psyche right now. No, no, no, I don't have to shut up
If I'd seen you if I'd seen you addicted would you worry about that in five years?
Well, no, I was like, you know, I put in my collection and I like, you know, look at her
Have your time and think about you
But you wouldn't fucking be all worried all the time and use it
as an excuse
Hi
How are you?
How are you Saki? How are you?
I'm very good
How are you?
I'm really good
How about you? You're good?
I'm good
I just wanted to make sure you're good
Do you know Russ?
Rusty. Yeah. Rusty. Hi, sweetheart. Hi, I don't think it's being an apple. Did I kick him in the balls?
Because I'm right. Oh, wait, I mean,
here we go with the fucking women team. I don't usually take the bait. I don't usually take the bait. But today I felt like it's Friday. I'm not working.
Oh, God, I did not come up here and tell the story of this piece of shit.
This total piece of shit. I'm not the only person that he did it to you. He's done it to other people that are
Relationships other women that are related
That's completely it's totally known to everyone these other women are in relationships and he's still
came on and started shit with them.
You're trying to break up relationships?
You're sitting here.
She's breaking up relationships.
Wait, so Rampi and Vader are together,
and you're trying to break up the relationships?
Stiggy, what's going on here?
No, no, no, no, no.
Right.
Yeah.
No, that's not what I want to know.
She wants to break me and Jana up.
She wants to break me in.
Oh, no, you got jammed.
No, Jan, don't do that.
No, I'll dump her, dummy.
And fucking, she fucking hates Bader.
She hates Bader, too.
And that's weird, isn't it?
What did Bader do to you?
He didn't do anything.
He ran a stream threatening my life.
Oh, shit.
Oh
My question is why we're we're
He said he made dick pics. I mean it's like, you know, I got Barry several months ago
Like this story your life
Guys and also people keep saying oh, I sent you a dick pic and I go and it's like
Is it a picture of Andy?
I don't think Vader sent her a dick pic, but Vader
Didn't say he was going to destroy her life. Oh, yeah, I did. Oh, yeah, I did weird
Man, you're weird. It's been Vader. I like knowing I'm being like a huge sum. He's something for everybody
Yeah, Vader. Is that true? Vader. That's what I heard. I don't know. I already like you
Okay, what are you like this like you're scared of beta now. Okay. Okay. No, I'm not scared of it
I'm gonna take him to court. Oh
Why don't you take beta to court because you take
At this show
My life is probably pissed off because you keep taking
I don't know how leader got directed to this
As a as a United States citizen to file charges or file a protection order
No, they can't stop. No, you have taken everybody's case. No, that's what you do. You take
Rusty, I got you, okay? I'll take favor of the court for you so you don't have to get
on another thing beyond your record for taking people to court. Yeah, I'll do the dirty one.
I'm not the criminal when I take people to court. No, no, no, no. I mean, like you doing,
You know there's no there's no statute of limitations of how many projection orders I can file
Okay, she knows a lot
The last person she took on it was this miss so Vader will be fine
Okay, well nothing was dismissed. I think psyche's like alright. Well, I'm glad this is resolved. He's
Little hammer I need a hammer
It's too far away
It's too far he's looking at it. He's like it's too far away
Trisha's in the way
Oh god, resty has eight people to go to yeah, let's see like, you know, it is expensive to keep taking maybe it's like, you know
Best not so she's got the money. She can do it
Money it cost me a hundred dollars to file a protection order
That's funny and then you lost doing these people. I'm following protection orders on them so that they have to go to court and face me on zoom court
That's the way it works when you can that's not I worked the last time
So then you can do it on your own like if it's across whatever how do you serve them though?
Uh the cops she she calls the cops
Yeah, but what if like they don't open the door and they're never served
You can't if you you can only do that for so then I win automatically
Oh, really?
Yeah, I mean like how do you win?
Are I'm using defamation against mr. Beast
Papa protection order on you and you refuse to get the papers and I automatically win. That's the way it goes
That joke would be nice to rest here. She'll probably sue you
Down here down the south we always say lawyer
I got my lawyer already y'all up in the north y'all say a lawyer
So who is rusty are you rusty?
Yeah
like a rusty old raggedy piece of metal. She doesn't like penis and she's uh no I just don't like your penis. I just don't like your penis. What happens when you when you like let's say that like a piece of like old metal like scrapes you what do you call that?
Something like that because the metal what's it called tonight a tech shop
Tech shop techno shop. No techno shot. Yeah, you're gonna give me a shot of techno
I'll give a shot of AIDS one day
I beat on you better be quiet. I like you
They make me look great. They're probably much more the crazy you are
What are you doing Joker? Have you been?
But something in your curls and make them into Jerry pearls. No tinnitus is in the years. It's not called tinnitus
Take pack not tonight is tech. I shot take savvy shots
Yeah
I know my English is a little bit bad, but I'm not sorry.
Oh, tetanus, tetanus shot.
Tetanus, tetanus shot.
They only have to be that, like an accurate tetanus.
Okay, so tetanus is a serious disease of the nervous system
caused by a toxin-producing bacterium.
Where should I feel the rusty house right now? That's what I think, but okay. It can cause painful muscle spasms and can lead to
On the live
This is potentially a fatal bacteria infection that affects the nerves a vaccine can you leave prevent the infection?
muscle spasms
This is Jan your ex-girlfriend Ziggy
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
I'm a graduate, I'm a graduate, I'm a graduate.
Look at you, you've got a belly now, fucking.
What happened to you?
Yeah, fucking Joker, you've got a big belly after.
I'm a graduate.
Damn.
He's got to be waiting. He's got to be waiting. That's what he's doing.
Nick, over there exercise. I think he takes like a, it's his line.
Nick has a great body. You got to do that.
That's a boy blue.
What?
That's our boy blue.
A boy blue?
That's Nick Johnson.
I don't know who blew this.
I fucking love this.
This is great.
I fucking love it.
You're easily amused.
I'm getting more drunk.
This is great.
Okay, we're looking at the satanic sign. That's it. Yeah, why did Joker go Joker always like dips out Joker
Oh, he's here. He's here. He does is he just
What do you mean? I know
Okay
He doesn't like it when you leave the panel. He's here for you psyche. I'm sorry. No, it's here. We're here for each other. That's how we work here right here for me to here for me song song.
Okay.
I'm a Virgo. Oh, he's a Virgo.
The link is the Virgo. I'm a Virgo.
You're ready to go. I get ready.
You're a Virgo. You never get laid.
Okay, got you.
I'm going to kick. I'm a Virgo.
No, I like that
When I was like in elementary school and I lost in a middle school
I didn't actually didn't talk when I'm still I was like five. That's kind of weird. So you just lost
Are you 15 or 16 I'm a I'm a guy. She's mean she's mean man. She's a mean woman
You're being are you being mean rest is the joker?
She's totally mean
Be the group
Carpenters board or the right you John?
No, it's one of the graduation. Well, I use yeah, I used to be
What does that mean what does that mean it's a handmade thing. Oh
It's a handmade
Are you like a one?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
I'm really sorry about that. You know, I tried not to do that. I apologize. No
His dick unsolicited to you she's one of the
Just send it to spiky and he likes to, you know, just have it, send it over there.
Joker, what the fuck happened to your belly?
You were in pregnant like a month ago. This is way too far.
It's further to the room.
Let's say the back joker.
He's in the second now.
It's not working.
are poor Joker
It might be Elizabeth Moss, but it does look like her eyes
That's why I was confused. Oh
You can't say anything like that Rusty
You don't even know what the hell fucking blue to fucking shade is you have no talking about I know what jammery looks like
whatever dude see you make any sense now you f**king idiot
stop bad shaming me stop bad shaming me
where is good times to look at those good times to watch them
mowing the lawn
so you gotta get a tetanus
tetanus
What is that nail in your butt? What happened? You got I don't know. I'm joking. What a joke. What a joke. What about what about tight anus Joker?
You're talking about yourself. So there's a person in the chat or certain person on the panel named rusty
She's a rusty piece of metal. So the only way to like get rid of her is to get a
He's an ass man. He's an ass man. Well, maybe that too, but I like how Rusty likes to call
What's that? I think I see what she looks like. Does she look like a rusty piece of model? She never will.
How do you know this isn't me?
Are you share?
That's her in here. She has a pretty face though. She's so hot. Is that her guys?
Yeah
Whatever you got it you look at you look like share
Thank you. If I could tell
What's I got you baby? We're saying I got you baby. I say wasn't you good? I think I just needed
What'd you do oh excuse yourself?
Oh
Like a smooth face
You know you know King can you?
No, it's the Canadian
Well Joker hey beat up you talk to Joker a while Joker's here
Ziggy, do you know Joker?
I don't know. Is everyone awake
I think I'm gonna show my I think I'm gonna show my penis. So she
Know my show I got to take care of my dogs
Okay, I think I think you I think you've shown your penis enough for a lifetime
Yeah
It's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it
There's
This situation with
Taking a picture of an actual hard-on didn't actually happen with this idiot
Okay, can't get a fucking whole full hard-on because he's an alcoholic
So like whatever you see and like a young man with an erect penis
whatever it doesn't even matter what the size is. Oh you don't know Rusty would you
tell that it's ready to go if you know what I mean but this guy can't produce a picture of a dick
that's ready to go. Okay Rusty would you want to see it in real life right now?
On this camera
Nobody wants to see it because I have to tell you or ask like a general question you said you wanted to see it
And I don't want to offend anybody. I don't want to offend anybody if this is a real situation like you actually have
Where you
Your person that goes to chatter
You know an exhibitionist type person and you know what's going to happen on chatter bait and you know what's going to happen on the other end of the screen.
So you don't have like any inhibitions if as far as that's concerned.
But I got to tell you the average person that brags about flapping on lane with another person.
It's awkward as fuck. It doesn't happen.
The majority of the time.
It's very in my oh, thank you Joe. It's a lot of braggadoce. It's bullshit. It's a lot
For intimacy with another person it's awkward as fuck unless you've been with that person
A real connection to where that's where you're gonna go, but
So Ziggy, are you going to start a chat or beta account and then I can watch you?
No, man, like she's so crazy like dude, listen this woman that was talking she's always gonna be single
And it's unfortunate that I'm not single now. I'm not single now, I have never been single, I've never been single, I've never been single, I've never been single, I've never been single, I've never been single, I've never been single, I've never been single, I've never been single, I've never been single, I've never been single, I've never been single, I've never been single, I've never been single, I've never been single, I've never been single, I've never been single, I've never been single, I've never been single, I've never been single, I've never been single, I've never been single, I've never been single, I've never been single, I've never been single, I've never been single, I've never been single, I've never been single, I've never been single, I've never been single, I've never been single, I've never been single, I've never been single, I've never been single, I've
We're having a great time because it's not on YouTube and you never will be
And coming from somebody
You're also probably going to be alone forever.
So you shouldn't throw stones at others.
Your chickens are named Rusty's.
Right now, your chickens are named Rusty's.
Yes, they are.
Because I like Rusty and I like chicken.
I know.
It is the same problem.
But you're like excited fucking crab.
What?
Will you guys stop fighting like you're a fucking married
ex-coupler or something?
All right.
We are.
Shut up.
Look at you
We never even met I thought like okay the person that just joined I thought it was chicken
All right, yeah, wait, who are you? Hi?
It's it is me. It's in
Well, why are you so different today?
And you change your picture I was like you're so quiet
I just got done. Oh, I just got done with the girl friends. Get ready. What is the fucking problem, dude?
Do you have a problem with us talking about the sound of my voice?
Is that Barley? I'm like Jen. I just wanted to hear your voice like I was like she was so quiet. I was like, hey, is that Jen or...
Fuck you, Zadies. Anyway, sorry. Go on, you guys. I'm trying to follow up.
What the fuck? Why'd you tell me that? What the fuck? I was saying, huh?
That's because, all right, I'm just going to give you an idea of what I'm asking you guys to continue.
So, how much do you want Jan back now?
Hi.
Oh, no.
I think, uh, I think I think the guys, I think, uh, the burpees, I got them. I'm not sure. Maybe there's a little bit of burpees. It's not too bad.
Audio isn't no, it's not you. It's not I think I think I think because I don't hear it now
Okay, cuz usually it is me like I've heard myself on the playback before and I'm like
I'm able to go into the mic settings. Okay. Yeah, so I fixed it. I think I just adjusted
I just said reset the mic. Yeah. Yeah. Hey, thanks. Good looking out. Good job. Oh, no problem. I have five gold star
Yeah
Hi guys
How's everyone chat so guys we had a lot of members added like a ton of members like I think we added like 20 in the past couple days
Yeah, I had a bunch and like, you know, but a bunch of people don't be how many members did you have added?
How do you laugh with her, that's funny and that's why you're single now.
stupid as fuck yes I'm single yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah I'm single yeah yep yep
no I'm talking to the bear yeah he's talking forever I hate men I'm so done
I know you are it's okay it's all right
You never had any intention
I was just a fucking game I can admit that I'm a grown person. I know what this is. So I was just a fucking game
No, I'm not a game with her. No, I'm not I'm chatting. I'm chatting with my buddy
That's what it is
Dude, he doesn't have any friends, he doesn't have any friends, he doesn't have anybody to giggle with, he doesn't have anybody to talk to, he doesn't have anybody to talk to, he doesn't have anybody to talk to, he doesn't have anybody to talk to, he doesn't have anybody to talk to, he doesn't have anybody to talk to, he doesn't have anybody to talk to, he doesn't have anybody to talk to, he doesn't have anybody to talk to, he doesn't have anybody to talk to, he doesn't have anybody to talk to, he doesn't have anybody to talk to, he doesn't have anybody to talk to, he doesn't have anybody to talk to, he doesn't have anybody to talk to, he doesn't have anybody to talk to, he doesn't have anybody to talk to, he doesn't have anybody to talk to, he doesn't have anybody to talk to, he doesn't have anybody to talk to, he doesn't have anybody to talk to, he doesn't have anybody to talk to
What a fucking lucky guy he was that he had a woman that gave her gave him her time her energy
Her caring you under the fan what I just said you whatever it was that you had
you're a piece of shit, you're a quantity twist,
it's alright.
Evil narcissists, so this is your life.
This is your life.
No, this is your life.
This is exactly how you are.
A lack of being able to be together.
You little motherfucker.
You know it.
Everybody knows it.
I don't even have to say it.
Oh my god, can we just get along for five minutes? Come on guys. No, no, she and I, no
Shut up. You sound like a married couple right now
Lenore
I'm gonna like rusty one time
Wait, you like rusty and you also like John
You know a wise man once said in fact, I think it was Yoda
The big version of Yoda the original not the baby Yoda. He said there is no try. There is only do or do not
Yes
Very good. We got some Star Trek fans
Okay, sorry. I'm sorry. Hey Rusty. You didn't win buddy, but
Later. Well, it was not a game. Let's it be the fruit. Let's it be the fruit
Later. Okay. Psyche later, ma'am. Bye
Take it out. Let's it be the fruit. What are you going to find some friends because you don't have any?
Dumb fuck loser
person or something happened to Chris Hall, I don't think that we have the Chris Hall.
You see, Nicholas, we have the best-looking yard in his hood, yeah, look at how few things
come in so well.
Have you ever found a new Chris Hall?
Who's that?
What is that?
What am I watching right now?
Oh, this is just Nick doing some yard work, you know, he likes to just do some horticulture.
Horticulture?
Yeah, some landscape.
that's not what I'm talking about.
That's not what I'm talking about.
A little bit he's wearing nut huggers nut hugger shorts
If this cam had been in my yard this morning, I would have fallen bomb somebody because I apparently need to get a new pair of sweatpants.
I knew that this pair of sweatpants was kind of baggy, but I'll put them on anyway because they have pockets.
And I put my phone in one pocket and I put something else in another pocket and I had the leash in my hand.
a chicken feeder and don't you know,
and I was walking at the same time
and my pants slid all the way down to my knees.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, well, I used to love it.
Even at the women's magazines,
there's women's magazines,
they don't have the most embarrassing moments,
like in those women's magazines,
they have that, it would always be about like, oh, you know.
I just went to take my trash out like a couple days ago and I was wearing a dress and I don't know why like the back
Was tucked on my underwear and I didn't even know I went all the way took the trash out came back up
And I'm like why is my dress like why'd my yeah, I hope nobody saw it, but I think a couple people did
I've been pretty lucky. I've been pretty lucky to only have had incidences in the backyard a couple years ago
I had a colony of bees
it was my second year of bees my second hive and
They were nowhere near as docile as the previous hive that I had had.
Those bees, I would go out there in a tank top and just open the lid and pour their sugar water in.
But those were not.
And I went out there completely unprepared and not covered in anything except for a tank top and shorts and flip-flops.
And those bees lit me up and I was like running to the back door pulling clothes off. Oh my God. I ended up with like 27 bee stings.
Yeah.
Well, good.
And I was naked by the time I got to the back door.
Hello.
Good morning.
Why is that guy mowing his lawn?
Why is he stealing good times content?
Who is that fucking gay guy?
And Ziggy, why are you in the chat acting like you're in middle school, dude?
Because Rusty and I like to talk to each other.
We're best friends now.
Have you guys ever met each other? He doesn't have any. Well, you know what?
I can't I can't keep fighting with him while you're up here
Hey rusty rusty. Have you ever met Aaron before?
What do you mean in real life friends? How are you guys best friends you guys?
Nobody's met him in real life because he's a fucking loser
Never met each other. What do you mean? Never met each other
Don't try to get involved
No, this retard this retard Aaron. I don't know who the fuck you guys are this retard Aaron
Just said that you and her are like best friends or you and oh god damn I can't talk to anybody
Okay, so first of all, first of all, Aldi. Hi, my name is Jan. I, um, I've been involved
with, okay, this is Rusty.
This is this is my buddy Rusty. We know each other through this little community that we're in
There you go. He is pretending like we're best friends now because
We like to talk to each other. So he's one being childish. I'm not picking on your buddy. That's just my body
That's what's happening
Is your buddy who is he not?
Who Ziggy
Yeah, I thought he was talking about
You guys don't like each other
He dick writes you he drops your name
All the time
I don't really want to be involved, but I like you.
I like you.
And guess what?
Well, this is fucking happy Friday night.
That's rich, man.
She didn't do this bitch.
Fuck this guy, Ziggy.
Fuck him.
Beach, okay
All the what's wrong what all the what's wrong? You okay fuck I'm on
Peter I didn't call you a stamp. I said I heard from the grape vine you were I don't I wasn't saying I don't know
You know that you crashed on your scooter. Are you okay psyche? Yeah, I wasn't really I mean it was
Under his eye under his eye good everybody
I
Ziggy I just want to confirm
What time we going to good good time for me black black guy black guy, that's
Can't this was canceled
He said he didn't want people to go outside his house. No no he was telling people that because he didn't want to start an element growing
I had a conversation with him
He's got Van Halen coming
I think he said he was like
You said you said this guy's name. I'm not gonna call him God, bro. This guy's a black
Don't worry about what God's gonna do. Don't worry
All right, I don't know
But I'm pretty sure you think I'm gonna need a ride though. Just pick me up around six
I will man around six o'clock and we'll fucking show up. Yeah, don't don't bring the chickens this time. All right
No, but what we're going to do is, like, hey, man, don't bring guns.
Well, if he doesn't bring the chickens, what are you going to eat for dinner?
He's got to bring some of them.
Good times is going to have food there, obviously.
Good time says he's not
He said he said nobody's there. He said nobody's welcome
About an hour no one's going to be good
I'm ready you coming
I already paid all the fucking $30 from me for a ticket
Audi! Remember when you cried on Steve-o-o-o?
This is, this is Audi, right here.
Yo, Ziggy, I'm so impressed, I miss you, I miss you brother, Ziggy, you're a faggot, Ziggy.
Hey, hey, I was just kidding.
Alright, alright, that's fine, my bad, my bad site.
Fuck you.
Guys, Ziggy, any time Goodtimes bans me, you always fucking, you stay on his site cause you don't want to get banned either, bitch.
You're not a fucking real one, motherfucker.
Fuck you, Ziggy.
Go sit in the woods and join Goodtimes panel.
Okay.
That's bullshit.
$7.20.
Is it real?
I get it.
Yeah.
Fuck him. I don't know. Nobody said nobody said please every time he joins good time. He's like good time is my mom
With a 38 and I get good time
No, but the whole thing is coming there. Yeah, July 4th. What I fucking go
July 4th, he says he doesn't want people on this property
You know, he's has a party he's got a party. It's like he has a party like hope
I think you misunderstood he doesn't want gay guys
Oh, okay. It's okay. Oh, I'm not coming anyway. He said he was party but he doesn't want gay people at his party.
It's okay. It's okay. It's okay. It's okay. I heard Joe Shipley was going though.
He was ugly ass girls that are like rusty and beat us kiddies there. That's what he was.
Yeah
The fans are supposed to shake hands with Audi and fucking like all these people
I'll see you. Yeah, I'll see you like my little brother.
He's not a second, but I'm sorry, budget. He's a racist trying the little bro me. I
will. Yeah, I'll be I'll see you there. He's trying a little bro me sick, man. I'm your
Oh, you're brony Aaron Carter. Oh, Aaron Carter
My god has nobody seen
It's like it's like the yellow fucking so
That's a woman. That's a woman.
That's a woman's face. That's a woman's face.
Oh, I thought that was Aaron Carter.
I'm not joining into anything.
I'm having a conversation.
Right now you are.
Hey, I'm asking you what the name is.
What is the name about?
Well, you would have to have seen or know the show.
series The Handmaid's Tale. It came from a book. It's what is it called? Oh my God. The Handmaid's Tale.
Jesus Christ. The Handmaid's Tale. The Handmaid's Tale. Okay. So basically, they take, they take
It's not apocalyptic but there's a war and like the ultra-conservatives like take over everything and for some reason
The women can't have kids mostly because the men are sterile
So what they they start taking handmaids?
Damn man. That's a long time nabbing up fertile women and
converting them into handmaids and giving them to
like the commanders who are already thinking about that that was a long explanation so they take on
the name of whoever their commander is and it's all whoever their commander's name is hence all the
It's a whole, it's a whole, it's a whole literary reference that I guess you just picked the most attractive, you picked the most attractive commander.
I didn't have a choice. That's the whole point. It picked me.
Oh, if you're a little whore, huh? You're like a little slut. He wants to be
No, he's not harassing. He's not harassing. I know Audi he's okay
It's fine
No, no, no
Shut the fuck up dude
Telling me
and explaining things for me bro i can explain shit for myself ziggie shut the f**k off you man
fuck you shut up f**k you f**k you mother f**ker
you bitch in the woods listen to that f**k bitch
it was like this niggie shut up
f**k where f**k off and listen to her i'm not f**king to you
I'm talking to you, I'm not talking to you, why aren't you talking like that?
Fuck you, man.
Fuck you.
I don't give a fuck.
Talk to him.
Hey girl, 70 years old and she tried to put a filter over her picture to look like me.
Look at your picture. Look at your picture. She put she put a filter over her face
She's like 20 years older than me
Who what girl?
HG in the chat. She won't come on the piano. She won't she won't face me.
She's a star
She's obsessed obsessed with me. You're being where's the or being weird she wants to lick my sliz
Lick my sliz
How old is like the age
Don buddy
You've already said that a bunch of times like I don't know why you need to affirm it on panel in front of all these
I'm the one that's blocked to you. So, uh, you know, I don't really
Things let's think about other things come on howdy, what it's up. What are you doing? No, you don't control the conversation
because jen is a streamer jen has a channel that's interesting she's attractive she attracts
of women and men and she's a streamer and she couldn't stream when she was involved with you
because every time she tried to fucking stream you would throw a fucking fit and try to control
I watched damn right and the bottom line is you're too fucking dumb to stream. That's the bottom line
You can't even fucking talking about channel that streams. I'm talking to ziggy not you
Ziggy is too dumb to stream.
She'll get mouthy with you.
Don't talk to her.
So he goes around to all of the streamers
and tries to fucking get attention for himself
because he's too goddamn dumb to stream.
That's just the bottom line.
There we go.
Anyway.
Who's she talking about, Ziggy?
Yeah, it's a big plant. No, not really. Um, but it says 60% 60.5% males 39.4% females 21.
I knew it! I was right!
So I'm not screaming at anybody to shut up, but everybody in this side chat is whining
I'm going to insult the lady on
the panel so I could get
attention for myself while I'm
fapping to your voice. Oh my
god.
Thank you for being here.
You're ready. You're ready.
Yeah. Yeah. Anyway.
Shut your fucking mouth.
Yeah, I don't know if I could anybody want to come on for a panel because I don't I don't know
I don't want you guys just fighting
How are you doing? You look good. I'm chilling bro. I just it's fucking annoying one person's trying to talk and then
Ziggy you need to stop cutting people off you fucking
Oh if Aaron you're dumbass I could tell that you're fucking uh like I like no offense you sound
You're acting like fucking like you think that you know everything. What was that shit that we
You're
I don't care for a girl I learned I learned everything from Aldi
Aldi, what do you think of flirty diamonds?
Aldi Aldi, what do you think of flirty diamonds? Did you hear flirty diamonds with raging demon now?
I'm never
Okay, wait, I'll have a question. I have a question because I I only catch like snippets and what's going on
Yeah, throughout the day when different
For reference point slurdy diamond is that a male?
That's a man. That's a man.
That's a whole nigga.
Well
Like an Indian man
like man she's crazy I'm glad I'm not with her thank god well she's she's a
very nice person and she's but you know what would you rate flirty diamonds from
one to ten sites well I think she's a lovely person I mean she's a good-looking
Well, you know, I think, you know, I'll admit are attractive, you know, this is most annoying piano. Oh my gosh
One more last question, I'll be quiet for a while
Last question
Hey, what's up KZ
Hey, what's going on? Yeah, I hate to say this but like Jim won't even be on that like three
scalping like I would say like fuck mary johan okay no i don't want to say i don't want to say i don't want to say i don't want to say i don't want to say i don't want to say i don't want to say i don't want to say i don't want to say i don't want to say i don't want to say i don't want to say i don't want to say i don't want to say i don't want to say i don't want to say i don't want to say i don't want to say i don't want to say i don't want to say i don't want to say i don't want to say i don't want to say i don't want to say i don't want to say i don't want to say i don't want to say i don't want to say i don't want to say i don't want to say i don't want to say i don't want to say i don't want to say i don't want to say i don't want
Yeah, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
I'll be. I'll be, I'll be I'll be, I'll be, I'll be, I'll be, I'll be, I'll be, I'll be, I'll be, I'll be, I'll be, I'll be, I'll be, I'll be, I'll be, I'll be, I'll be, I'll be, I'll be, I'll be, I'll be, I'll be, I'll be, I'll be, I'll be, I'll be, I'll be, I'll be, I'll be, I'll be, I'll be, I'll be, I'll be, I'll be, I'll be, I'll be, I'll be, I'll be, I'll be, I'll be, I'll be, I'll be, I'll be, I'll be, I'll be, I'll be, I'll be, I'll be, I'll be, I'll be, I'll be, I'll be, I'll be, I'll be,
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,